三个火枪手
改编自大仲马的小说
"Based on the novel by Alexandre Dumas".
怎么样!
So!
当你再没办法的时候 无论你看见什么
Whatever you see just last your sword when all allow is failed.
- 这帮了我很大的忙 正如你看到的 - 是的 父亲
- It was helped me well, as you can see. - Yes, Father.
- 您为什么不坐一下呢? - 不不不 时间很紧迫了
- why don't you sit down, sir? - no, no, no, time is short.
你要走了
you must be off.
我把我的秘密武器给你
I'm giving you my secret threats.
还给你这1万5千元
I give you also these 15 grands.
还有这个
And this.
你爷爷买了这把剑来对付勒班陀的摩尔人
Your grandfather bought this sword against the Moors in Lepanto.
我曾经也用过它 在国王亨利统治的时候
I'm in some use of it, under the lead of King's Henry.
现在它是你的了
Now it is yours.
它会带你去拜见火枪手的领导者特雷威尔先生
It will introduce you to Mr. Treville who command the king of Musketeers.
你会永远记住它的 我也会
you will remember it well, and me.
给你
Here...
我的儿子啊 你快成为一个火枪手了
My son, you are gonna be a Musketeer.
你年轻 应该要勇敢 如果你有勇气的话
You are yong you should be brave, and if your guts' strong.
而且你叫达塔尼昂
And the D'Artagnan.
所以 该打的时候就打
So fight whenever you can.
不要屈服于凌辱
Never summit to insalts.
除了国王和红衣主教的
except from the king and the Cardinal Richelieu.
要小心红衣主教 因为他是通过国王来统治法国的
Beware of the cardinal, for he rules France through the king.
但是你是为效忠于国王和皇后的人
But you are a King's man and the Queen's.
好了
So...
现在去和你母亲说再见吧
Now go and say goodbye to your mother.
你的膏药在包里
Your balm is in the package.
在你伤口上涂上就好
Rup it in wherever you scratch.
我在你的鞋子里面装了轮子
I'm driving the wheels in you shoes well.
好的 母亲 再见
Yes, mother, good-bye.
再见 父亲
Good-bye, father.
再见
Bye.
不要把马卖了 让它老死吧
Don't sell the horse! Let him die old of its own age.
记得要战斗啊
and fight remember!
保重
Take care!
听话
Come on!
看准了
get on it.
看起来有人骑在一只茶杯上
Sighted there's someone riding above the cup.
好像一块有脚的芝士
That's just a cheese with legs.
如果你笑的话 你最好想想为什么
Think what you have laugh ,sir. And you laugh together.
如果是正在跟我说话
If you speak to me.
如果你不是一个绅士的话 我不会和你说话
If you weren't a gentleman I wouldn't speak to you.
我没和谁说话
I was speaking at tuteur.
但是我在和您说话啊
But I'm speaking to you sir.
如果你是个男人就转过身来
Turn if you are a man.
让我看看你现在倒是怎么笑
Let me see your laugh now.
啊
Ah.
这人真扯淡
This gascons.
你想让我干掉他吗?
Do you like cut his throat?
不
No.
他的马给处理掉 让他走吧
But among his ridiculous horse. Let him go.
没时间谈了 我的姑娘
No time to talk, my lady.
红衣主教命令你来英格兰
The cardinal command you to England.
你要让白金汉公爵离开伦敦了
Do you have to let him know the moment.
才让主教知道吗?
till the Buckingham leaves London?
然后呢?
And then?
我等待下一步指示
I'll wait further orders.
你呢?我什么时候才能再见到你?
And you? when do I see you again?
你...你这个刺客
You!You assasin!
我应该把你刺死的
I shall thrust die you, sir.
原谅我 女士 但是我必须把你朋友杀死
Forgive me, madam. But I must kill your friend.
噢 你不怕吗?
Oh, you're not terrified?
哈! 走开 白痴
Ha! Away! Pumpkin!
你会等到我消息的
You will hear from me.
他挺帅的
He's very handsome.
尽管他有些迟钝
Even though he is bluntness, maybe.
克劳德 付钱吧
Claude, pay the bill.
你...
You...
- 特雷威尔先生在哪儿? - 在楼上 跟我来
- Where is Mr. Treville? - He's upstairs, follow me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你太紧张那个腰带了
You are doing more on belt proper.
我有吗?
I do?
是啊
Oh, yes.
我曾经是个喜欢
I used to be a man who must.
每晚花钱在自己的衬衫上的男人
spent his money on fine shirts in the night.
什么?
what?
或者赚他情妇的钱?
or want his mistress' money?
哦 不 阿拉米斯那可是我自己的钱啊
Oh, no, Aramis help me out to get her but my own money.
那都是金币啊 那都是小事
all of these are pistoles, oh, this is all trifles.
但是 的确是拿我的金币在床周围围了一圈啊
but it is gold building all the way around the bed.
太震惊了
Astonishing!
法国有足够的金子吗?
There is enough gold in France to straight or let her sense.
你介意我在抬起这珍贵的大衣多看一眼这腰带吗?
Mind if I lift the costly coat to admire the belt more?
不不不 先生
No, no, no, your pardon, sir.
我感冒了
I have a cold.
自由裁量权都变成虚荣的时尚了
Discretion being a part of vanity.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我知道我眉毛很好看
I know the one about valla...
但是我不知道眼神好
but it don't know eye contact will need.
会令眉毛的效果大打折扣
to be discrete half of that in time.
长太帅了就是没办法
shouldn't balost.
这剑十分干脆利落
It's very clean the sword dressed.
是红衣主教守卫队的纪念品啊 阿多斯先生
a souvenir of the Cardinal's Guard, Mr. Athos.
你是个骗子 真扯淡
You're a liar. That's more ballocks.
当然 你怎么这么快就看出来了?
Of course. Why do you see that immediately?
不要假装在你这里每一个人
Don't pretended one from another.
都得到不同的待遇
or make any difference to a treament if you did.
特雷威尔先生现在要见你了
Mr. Treville will see you now.
啊
Ah.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你老子说你带着他自己的剑吧 达特尼昂先生
Your father says you carried his own sword Mr. D'Artagnan.
是的
Yes.
嗯嗯
Hum hum.
哦
Oh.
你可以带着我的家伙 等你的再长长点之前
You may have taking my arm along until yours grows longer.
先生 我不要任何人的怜悯
Sir, I ask charity for no one.
那就是说你不会拿 是吧?年轻人
Then you're unlikely to get it. Are you, young man?
不 不是怜悯
No, not charity.
是出于对老友儿子的一点爱和小恩惠
Love and courtesy for the son of an old friend.
让他的敌人在大洋彼岸 哪儿凉快哪儿呆去
to keep his enemies that in shore to far enough.
谢谢您 先生
Thank you, sir.
真谢谢您
I do thank you.
那是我能给你的所有了
That is as much as I can offer you.
你看到了 剑客里面没有空位置安排给你了
You see there is no place in the musketeers.
只有你在军队里面服役过
for a man till he has served the campaign.
或者在其他的战斗方面立过大功
or other ways distinguishes himself in the killing.
但是我还是可以给德拉塞尔先生写封信
But all I can do is write a letter to Mr. De La Salle.
他是守卫的领导人
commander of the guard.
你...你这个懦夫 我鄙视你
You, you coward, I spit on you!
什么?
what?
哦不 说的不是您
Oh, not on you, sir.
说的是那个独眼龙
on that man without the eye!
你 先生
You, sir.
我让你站住
I said stop sir.
呀
Yah.
哦
Oh.
对不起 先生 我赶时间
Excuse me, sir. I'm in a hurry.
你当然很赶时间了 年轻人
You are certainly in a hurry, young man.
我的意思是 一句"对不起"是不够的
You heard that I mean to expect the "excuse me" is insufficient.
你需要有人教教你怎么有礼貌
You need a lesson in manners.
我说过"对不起"了
I said "Excuse me".
我不需要有人教我懂礼貌
I need no lesson in manners.
无论如何 你还是需要的
You should have one anyway.
哪儿?
Where?
12点在加尔默罗女修道会
The Carmelite convent, at twelve.
噢
Oh.
兜兜转转
Go all the way around.
停
Stop!
- 先生 我在跑着呢 - 而且眼睛还瞎了
- Sir, I was running. - And with your eyes shut.
- 先生 您说什么? - 你去中心广场
- Sir, I beg your pardon? - You will come to the Plaza.
- 哪儿? - 一点钟 在卢森堡
- Where? - At the Luxembourg one o'clock.
噢 看啊
Oh, look.
原谅我 先生们
Forgive me, gentlemen.
噢 您好像 掉了这个
Oh, you probably...you, you drop this.
金子的包装够花哨 最好小心点 阿拉米斯
Gold for the parcing fancy, most "discreet", Aramis.
这个包不是我的 也不是我掉的
The purse is not mine, sir, nor did I drop it.
这个就是您的 我看见他掉了
Oh, your parcel, sir. I see it fall.
你看到的太多了 先生
You see it the old too much, sir.
你只是一个乡下佬而已
You just a fourtmat country bad people.
我就是乡下佬 怎么了
I'm the gascon, sir.
所以你要学习更写文明的行为举止
And you need to learn civilized behavior.
好吧 我也不是一个仗势凌人的人
Well, I'm no bully. It's in the intended priest.
即使必须的 但是我也不想动手
I fight to even I must.
但是你让那位女士受委屈了
But you have compromised the lady.
那我们就约两点在特雷威尔酒店吧
So we'll set in hotel Treville at two.
先生 先生
Sir! Sir!
你的钱包
Your purse.
好吧 即使我被杀了 也是死在剑客手里
Oh well, if I will be killed, unleast at hands of a musketeer.
你挺准时的
You punctual.
即使你不用跑的
Eventhough you're not running.
但是你还是伤了我的胳膊
But you did hurt my shoulder.
我相信这样子打肯定对您来说 非常不方便
I trust that it will not convenient you sir.
如果你想推迟决斗
If you wish to prospone on meeting.
不可能
By no means.
我用左手一样可以打
I fight as well with my left hand.
如果你觉得这个地方对你来说处劣势 我道歉
If you find this place you'll be disadvantageous, I do apologize.
您真是非常谦虚
You're very courteous, sir.
我正准备问您的伤口
I was going to ask about your wound.
我带着我麻麻做的药膏
I have an ointment made by my mom.
嗯?
Hum?
你是被吓到了吗?年轻人
You're overwhelming, young man.
哦 我的帮手们来了
Oh, here come my seconds.
你要和这个乡巴佬打架吗?我也约了他干架呢
You're fighting this out fellow, but I'm meeting him myself.
但是现在不是一点钟啊
But not till 1 o'clock, sir.
不不不 我下午要和这个人决斗
No, no, no, I'm to fighting him this afternoon.
是在两点吧
At 2 o'clock sir.
你在巴黎多久了?
How long have you been in paris.
从今早上八点钟开始就在这儿了
Since 8 o'clock this morning.
你真是一点儿时间都没有浪费啊
You waste little time, sir.
我父亲教育我说该打就打
My father recommand I fight dues.
好吧 我们来希望你能你老子挣点面子吧
Well, let us hope you can do him some credit.
红衣主教护卫队
The cardinal's guard!
哎 快点啊 你们
Cheers, gentlemen, quickly.
啊 是剑客们 在法令的禁止下还在决斗
Ah, musketeers! Dealing in the founds of the edicts.
这是私事 麦迪逊 你这次可以绕路吗?
This is private, Madison. Would you please beyondyour way.
我们有责任维护法令
We have the duty the suppress his order.
和逮捕肇事者
and the arrest the rollers.
把你的的剑都举起来 然后跟着我们走吧
Put up your swords, and come along with us.
不可能
Impossible!
想都别想
Unthinkable!
没希望
Unlikely!
嗯 那我们要检举你们了
Hum, then we must charge you.
他们有六个 我们只有三个
There are 6 of them, we are only 3.
不 四个
No, 4.
你不是我们其中一员
You are not one of us!
这不关你的事孩子
This is not your affair, boy.
我也许不够技术 但是我有当剑客的决心啊
I may not have the tuny, but I have the heart to be a musketeer.
年轻人你可以退下了
Young man, you may retire!
保命为上吧 快走开
Save your skin, and quickly.
- 你叫什么? - 达特尼昂 - 那好吧
- What is your name? - D'Artagnan - Well then.
我们四个: 阿多斯 波尔多斯 阿拉米斯和达特尼昂
You have us, four of us:Athos, Porthos, Aramis and D'Artagnan.
杀啊
Go!
我们来祈祷吧
Let us pray.
善良的耶稣
Gentle Jesus...
我可以吗?
May I?
抱歉
Sorry.
给我把剑
A sword!
看上帝份儿上
For god's sake sir.
谢谢你
Thank you.
达特尼昂
D'Artagnan!
不
No!
不 把他留给我
No! Leave him to me.
把剑放下 先生
Put down your sword, sir.
不
No.
投降吧 我命令你
Surrender Biscart, my order.
哦 那倒不一样
Oh, that's different.
去把铃摇响吧 那些修女回来治你们的伤的
Come and ring the bell, the nun will attend to your wounded.
来 兄弟们 快走 越快越好
Come, gentlemen, the sooner and off the better.
对啊 对啊 结束太快了
Yes, yes, it was over too soon.
啊 娘的
Ah blood!
看着最好的弗兰德天鹅绒被你们毁了
Look at the best flemish velvet ruined by your...
被你们这些恶心的二货给毁了
your sick kind of ruffiers.
哦 天啊 你们要赔啊
Oh, my god. You will pay for it.
这花了我10个金币呢
10 pistoles it costed me.
不 20个金币 再加20个当做教你们怎么懂礼貌的学费
No, 20, 20 pistoles. And 20 more is a fine to teach you manners.
哈哈 这群草包
Ha ha, you sack!
小偷
Thief.
你说什么?
What?
好了 好了
There, there.
"乐善好施"是红衣主教的其中一个品质 是吧?
Charity is one of the Cardinal virtue, remember?
我们是要站这儿一直聊
Are we gonna stand here and chat.
等主教来逮捕我们回去吗?
until the Cardinal marshal come arrest us.
我们最好走吧 各位
Better be gone, gentlemen. I tell you.
我们走
Let's be off.
呃 先生
Er, sir.
你朋友们的伤
About your friends wounds.
我有我麻麻的膏药
I have an ointment adhere my mother which.
对伤病是最管用的
whether you mind its most effective.
我把剑扔天上 然后那个二货往上看
I threw my sword in the air, and as he looks up.
波尔多斯 波尔多斯
Porthos! Porthos!
把金币给我看看
Pass me the pistoles.
剑客们的座右铭是
The Musketeers' motto young man is:.
兄弟同心 其利断金
All for one and one for all.
我们给他10个金币
What should translate is ten for him,
10个给他 10个给你 10个给我
ten for him, ten for you, and ten for me.
我亲爱的阿拉米斯需要10个来取悦他的情人
My dear Aramis needs ten to impress his lady mistress.
我的好波尔多斯需要10个来买他的衣服
My good Porthos needs ten to be able himself to dress decently.
我建议你需要10个来找个仆人和住的房子
And you need ten for lodging and a servant I would suggest.
而我呢
And I.
你呢?
And you?
我需要喝酒
I need to drink.
你会发现 未来在喝醉了酒以后 会变得非常美好
You will find young man the future looks rosy at the bottom of the glass.
别担心 亲爱的
Not to worry, dear.
我抓住你的头
Let me catch your head.
小心点儿
Mind that.
这是楼梯
This is the staircase.
你应该会喜欢这儿的先生 两法郎一天而已
I think you'll like it here, monsieur. For only two francs a day.
这房间看起来真是非常豪华
This chamber looks Snohomish.
而且你仔细瞧瞧 非常的干净
And scrupulously clean if you observe.
每隔一天就会打扫一次
Swopt every second day.
谦虚一点说 真是帝王般的享受啊
and more regent the modest speaking.
啊 有点灰尘 你可以睡外面
Ah, there are rusgle. You can sleep out there.
隔音效果很好 外面的叫声完全听不到
effect of soundproof there is excellent. The scream will cast behind.
在巴黎 老天都掉不下来这样的馅饼啊
They don't fall of these chambers like these in Paris.
这儿你还可以看到非常好的城市景观
Where else you can get the magnificent view of the city.
噢
Oh.
的确如此 但是请原谅我说的话
Quite so, Mr Bonacieux, admit me is too absurd.
但是这个你叫做房间的地方真是不适合…
but this fixture you call a room is not fit for our.
国王或者大主教住但是很适合我
king or a cardinal but it suit me very well.
你说两法郎吗?
two francs you say?
- 你要了? - 怎么样我都要
- You take it? - whatever it's offered.
啊 我的老婆 伯纳修太太啊 先生
Ah, Madam Bonacieux, my wife, monsieur.
她很正吧
Is she not beautiful?
很有魅力啊
Enchanting.
谢谢
Thank you.
像花瓣从很远的地方撒向人间一样
She's as delicate as the petals pouring.
精致
From afar.
你知道吗?我老婆是皇后的伴娘呢
Of course, you know my wife is the best maid of the queen.
皇后是个很好的人 我妻子有足够的自信和她媲美
Very nice person the queen. My wife has every confidence.
我真是非常骄傲能成为她的丈夫
Yes I am very proud of being her husband.
- 她住这儿? - 不 我住这儿
- And...she live here? - No, I live here.
我美丽的康斯坦丝住在皇宫啊 要不然住哪儿?
My beautiful Constance Stays in the palace. where else?
她一周来看我一次
she visits me once a week.
就在今晚
Tonight, in fact.
- 夫人一定非常向往这一天 - 是啊
- Madam must look forward to that eagerly. - Yes.
噢 快点啊 你好笨
Oh, faster, you dull!
哦 快啊 快找人把它们转得快一点
Oh, come on, somebody make them go faster with them.
哦 太奇妙了 真是太奇妙了
Oh, it's wonderful. It's absolutely wonderful.
我觉得我想吐
I feel like, I feel like sick.
皇后到国王的骑士四号位
Queen to king's knight 4.
你的手下特雷威尔打倒了五个主教护卫
Your ruffians Treville has spite 5 of the Cardinal guards.
陛下 是您的火枪手们
Your Musketeers, my Majesty.
是你养的流氓
Your ruffians.
骑士到国王的主教五号位
Knight to king's bishop 5.
我很难对他解释
I'm hard to put to explain to him.
当我睡觉的时候 是谁在守卫着法国?
who guards France when I sleep.
当我在自我娱乐的时候 是谁在不断的工作?
whose larbors were unceasingly while I amuse myself.
您受命于天吗?
Your Mejesty refers to god?
我受命于红衣主教 和你说的不是那么一回事儿
I refer to Cardinal Richelieu, which is not quite the same thing.
哦 主教
Oh, Cardinal.
这起剑客暴乱事件
This matter of tribute musketeers.
没有头绪 只有几把断剑
Broken heads and broken swords.
只是琐事而已陛下
Trifles sire.
白金汉伯爵在巴黎了
The Duke Buckingham is in Paris.
白金汉?在这儿?为什么啊?
Buckingham ? Here? Why, God's name?
- 要和我起冲突吗? - 为了的皇后吗
- Oh, to bloods against my honor? - The queen?
- 你把那个恶棍抓回来 - 陛下 您错了
- You will arrested the potla. - Sire, you are wrong.
皇后对你很忠诚 对法国也很忠诚
The Queen is faithful, to you and to France.
她爱你爱的非常热烈
She loves your Majesty far too warmly.
我不会被热情所蒙蔽的 你抓住他
I'm not squat by the heat. You arrest him.
我们为什么要花这么大的精力做那事儿呢?
Oh, why the scandal should we do that?
逮捕英国的首相?
Arrest the Prime Minister of England?
没有理由陛下 我们需要做的是把尊贵的爵士
No, sire. What we must do is keep the noble duke.
栓在一根绳子上让他继续和新教徒追求他的信仰
on a string, to pursue his sodium pad with Protestants.
和他的看不见的政治理想
his politics muffled in a cloak.
那皇后的心 是否也无法摸透呢?
And the queen muffled in her cloak under a window?
皇后殿下的美貌 让很多男人拜倒在她的石榴裙下
Her Majesty's beauty affects all the men's worship.
也有很多支持者
And worshipers.
但是她的美德是毋庸置疑的
But her virtues is beyond questions.
至于白金汉公爵 他会被监视着的
As the Duke of Buckingham, he will be watched.
主教到皇后二号位
Bishop to queen 2.
将军
Jaque.
那边
That way.
开门
Open up!
再不开我们就把门撞开了
We will strike the door down.
啊
Ah.
- 有人要进来? 别担心 等我抄家伙 - 哦 亲爱的
- Did someone's coming? Don't worry, Constance. The weapons...- Oh, darling.
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha.
你得跟我走
You will come with me.
不 我不走! 我不走 你能把我怎么样?
No, I won't. No, I won't. We see, what about that?
你跟我走吧
You will come with me.
好的 先生 好的 先生我跟您走
Yes, sir, yes, sir. I come with you.
截住她 截住她
Stop Her! Stop Her!
你对我老婆做了什么?
What have you done with my wife?
康斯坦丝?
Constance?
达塔尼昂先生 我要你
Mr. D'Artagnan, I want you.
我是你的女士 等我喘过气来
I'm yours Ma'am. As soon as I can catch my breath ma'am.
- 我伤到你了吗? - 我伤到你了吗?
- Did I hurt you? - Did I hurt you?
先生 我今晚一定要去皇后那里
Monsieur, I must get to the queen tonight.
我不允许
I can not allow it.
- 我被人从床上拖下来了- 床是对你最好的地方了
- I was torn from the bed. - The best place for you, bed.
床就是对于你来说最好的地方了
Bed is the best place for you.
来着躺会吧
Collect some for more.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you monsieur.
哦 我的丈夫
Oh, my husband.
哪儿?
Where?
在巴士底狱
In the Bastille.
哦 真是令人担心啊
Oh, I'm sorry to hear about it.
现在最好的解决办法 就是睡个好觉
Now the best possible course is a good night sleep.
尝试忘记它
Try to foget about it.
- 但是我丈夫在巴士底狱我无法睡着啊 - 不
- But I can't sleep with my husband in the Bastille. - No.
- 我好怕 - 哦 我不怕
- I'm frightened. - Oh, I'm not.
你应该和我睡
You ought to sleep with me.
你需要一个帮你驱赶恐惧的人
You need a good cattle chase the fright away.
先生 我必须去皇后陛下身边 她迫切需要我
Mister, I must go to her Majesty, she needs me urgently.
我不能让你一个人在充满危险的大街上走
I can not let you go to the streets are full of danger.
而且你的脚都脏脏的
and your legs and feets are dirty.
哦…是啊
Oh... yes.
先生 你必须要帮我啊 你又年轻又勇敢
Monsieur, you must help me. You are young and gallant.
我丈夫他非常懦弱 而且说到他...
My husband is just a weak man talk with me and...
我能告诉你吗?我能相信你吗?
Can I tell you? Can I trust you?
用你跳动的心脏和生命去相信
With your life which beats in your breast.
我仿佛听到小白鸟挥打翅膀的声音
I hear the flap of life like a little white bird.
- 他通过我打听皇后 - 我听到充满生命力的翅膀拍打
- He sigints on the queen through me. - I hear the wings.
红衣主教希望给我个警示 因为我很皇后走得很近
Cardinal wishes a warning, because I'm in the queen's confidence.
或许他们会利用我来对皇后不利
perhaps yields to the attackers through me.
你不能光着脏脚去找皇后啊
You can not go to the Queen's with dirty legs.
哦 不行
Oh, no.
你现在有足够的力气下去洗干净吗?
Are you strong enough to wash them.
没有
No.
哦 我可怜的丈夫 没有了他我感到很无助啊
Oh, my poor husband. Without him I feel so helpless.
我还没试过给女人洗脚呢
I've never washed the legs of a woman.
我给马洗过脚 给马洗的时候 你要先从头开始
I have done a horse's, with a horse's you start at the top.
我不可以脏兮兮的去皇后那儿
I can not go dirty to the queen.
你觉得我在这儿会安全吗?
Do you think I will be safe here?
哦 当然了 康斯坦丝 当然了
Oh, yes, Constance. Yes.
哦 对不起
Oh, sorry.
这样不会有点冷吗?
Won't it not be a llittle cold?
至少让我送你过马路
At least, let me have got you pass the way.
不 我必须走
No, I must go.
- 去找皇后前 我要去见一个人 - 谁?
- I have to meet someone, before I go the queen. - Who?
这么快就学会妒忌了?
Are you jealous so soon?
那当然了
On every inch of you.
我必须走了现在 答应我你不会跟来
I must go now. Promise you won't follow.
哦
Oh.
给点钱盲人吧女士 你是瞎的吗?
Money for the blind ma'am. Are you blind?
给点钱瘸子吧 给点钱瘸子吧
Money for the cripple, Money for the cripple.
给点钱瘸子吧
Money for the cripple.
放开 走开
get off, go off.
给点钱瘸子吧 给点钱瘸子吧
Money for the cripple, Money for the cripple.
- 嘿 今天你不走运了 - 给点钱孤儿吧
- Hey, not your day, is it? - Money for an orphan!
施舍点钱给孤儿吧 给点钱孤儿吧
Money for a orphan, Money for a orphan.
嘘
shuh!
给点钱孤儿吧
Money for a orphan.
施舍点钱吧
Money, Money.
先生在您走之前
Before you go sir...
我说先生在你走之前
I say sir before you fight.
先生
sir.
施舍点零钱吧
If you got any change please.
请您等等 先生
One moment, sir. If you please.
你答应过我的
But you promised.
是的 现在我知道为什么你要我答应你了
Yes, and I can see now why you make me promise.
你和我不认识啊 先生
You have nothing to do with me, sir.
不认识 但是我和这位女士认识
No, but I have something to do with this lady.
抓着我的胳膊夫人 先生 晚上好
Take my arm madam. Good evening, sir.
- 天啊 我的公爵陛下 - 陛下? - 你是…?
- For god's name, my lord. - My lord? - Are you...?
白金汉公爵
The duke of Buckingham.
现在你知道你破坏了所有事儿了吧
Now do you see you spoil everything.
哦 亲爱的…原谅我吧…我...
Oh, my darling forgive me... I...
哦 陛下 我该说什么好…我…我爱她所以我妒忌
Oh, my lord, what do I say...I...I love her and I was jealous.
这是在黑夜里攻击一个陌生人非常好的原因
Perfectly exellent reason for attacking a stranger in the dark.
您能满足我一个小小的要求吗?
Would you obliged me in a small favour?
任何事都可以 陛下
Anything, my lord.
夫人和我打算去宫殿 并不想被任何人知道
Madam and I are going to the palace means not be seen.
如果有人想跟踪我们
If anyone should try to follow us.
您可以把他杀掉吗?
would you be good enough to kill him?
谢谢你
Thank you!
哦 好的…好的
Oh, yes ... yes.
你知道最危险的地方就是最安全的地方吗?
Does your Grace know any private place which is as private as this public one?
- 哦…我… - 在这儿等等 - 什么?
- Well ...I ... - Wait here. - What?
- 安妮… - 你怎么来了? - 来看你啊
- Anne ... - Why have you come? - To see you.
哦 你这个笨蛋!国王怀疑的
Oh, it's foolish! The King suspects.
而且大主教知道的话 你会害了我的
and the cardinal knows, and he'll ruin me if you can.
他派了很多眼线…如果他已经监视到这儿怎么办?
He spies the...what if he caught here?
很明显我们不会被发现 最起码在这个洗衣房里面
Decidedly we must not be found, not with the dirty laundry washed.
但是没有希望了 我是国王的妻子了
Oh but it's hopeless. I'm the wife of the king.
这个卑鄙的小人
And ill manner little prisey and.
忽略你 同时又嫉妒你
ignores you, and jealous you at the same time.
你欠了他什么?
What do you owe to him?
我欠了他 不能对不起他
I owe to him, not to disgrace him.
这也是为什么我让你走
Which is why I ask you to go.
而且不要回头
And not to return.
- 哦 亲爱的 我们不是一般的人啊 - 的确 我们不是
- Oh, my dear, we're not ordinary folk. - Indeed not.
这也是我们互相彼此伤害到对方的原因
And that's the point and it thrust both ways.
我不是一个绅士或者农民
I'm no little gentleman or farmboy.
我是一国之主啊
I'm the master of the great state there.
这个国家有非常强大的船只和海军 如果你需要我
with great ships and armies too, if you need me.
英国人从前来过法国
The English come to France before.
并没有像我现在拥有过这么充分的理由
A lack of better reason than I have.
你觉得我会因为赢得你而发动战争吗?
You think I will threat for a war to win you?
如果你不信 等着看法国挑起战争吧
If you doubt it, wait till Frances put his to draggle score the English for hell.
亲爱的 亲爱的安妮
Dear, dear Anne ...
你知道 你比任何我在洗衣房里面看到的东西都要美
Do you know, you look lovelier than anything I've seen in the laundry before?
来 再告诉我 你爱我
Come, tell me again that you love me.
你要走了 这里不安全
You must go. It's not safe here.
会有这么一天的 到了那天…
It will be oneday. Until then...
给点东西我留作纪念吧 一枚硬币 什么都可以
give me something to remember you by, a tocken, anything.
哦 求你了 你就当施舍给一个小穷孩儿吧
Oh, come, a farm boy, sweetheart you are giving one.
这些就是我最珍贵的东西了
These are my best things.
我一年之内会给你送回来
Within a year I will bring them back to you.
哦 她们就是这样洗衣服的 我从来都没有注意过
Oh, that's how they do it. I have no notion.
我以后穿衣服该怀着更尊敬的心情
I should wear my shirt in future with more respect.
- 哦 天啊 - 走啊 快点
- Oh, God! - Go on, quickly.
站着别动
Stand still!
在这里面
In here!
在那
There!
不好意思
Excuse me!
请告诉我发生什么事儿了
Please tell me what's going on.
过来
come here!
让我来吧 阁下
My lord, may I?
哦谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
来吧!来吧!
Come on! Come on!
哦我的头发
Oh, my hair.
我本来应该是能够应付的
I probably could have managed,
但是我还是得谢谢你们
but I'll thanks you gentlemen anyway.
- 那是谁? - 不知道啊
- And who is that? - I don't know.
- 但是他听起来说话很得体是吧? - 是啊
- But he sounded touch, warrant to me didn't he? - Yeah.
哦 天啊 这是怎么回事儿啊?
Oh, dear! What on earth is all about?
- 开始 - 我想跳下去 我什么都没干 我当时就躺床上
- Into go. - I want to jump. I did nothing. I was lying in bed.
我发誓我什么都没干! 他们准备对我怎样?
I swear I have done nothing, nothin! What do they do to me?
使尽手段 你在巴士底狱 你肯定干过坏事
Everything. You're in the Bastille. You must have done something.
你干的可是一级的叛国罪啊
What you have done is high treason.
你被指控串谋你的妻子和白金汉公爵
You are accused of conspiring with your wife and the Duke of Buckingham.
不不不
No, no...
你知道你是原告吗?
You know you are accuser?
谁把你带这儿来的?
Who brought you here?
那个 那个男人
That! That is the man!
- 带他走 - 不是那个
- Take him away. - That is not the man.
他是一个非常值得尊敬的绅士
He is a very honorable gentleman.
- 他们碰面了 皇后和白金汉公爵 - 在哪儿?
- They have met, the queen and Buckingham. - Where?
在宫殿里面 当我知道的时候已经太迟了
At the palace. I learn of this when it was too late.
你指...他在你指缝中溜走了?
You mean he slipped through your fingers?
事实上是在阁下的指缝中溜走了 我并没有下命令
In fact through your eminence fingers. I have no orders.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
那个叫伯纳修的女人把白金汉公爵带到巴黎了
The woman Bonacieux took Buckingham to the Paris.
伯纳修?我不是告诉你把她带回来吗?
The woman Bonacieux? I thought I told you to arrest him, to hold her.
被她她逃了 失败是常有的事
I failed. when does it occasionally.
如果我像你一样笨的话 我早就没命了
If I blunder as you do, my hand would fall.
阁下 我会把您的命看的比我自己的还珍贵
I would safe from greater high than mine eminence.
你会吗?
You would?
- 这是崇高的理想 - 你不怀有吗? - 没有
- The highter volting ambition. - You have none? - No.
- 你害怕我吗?罗什福尔 - 是的 阁下 害怕您
- You fear me, Rochefort? - Yes I fear you, eminence.
而且还恨你
I also hate you.
我爱你 我的孩子 即使你失败了
I love you, my son. Even when you fail.
皇后的确把有12颗珍珠的珍珠项链给了白金汉公爵
I do know the queen gave Buckingham the 12 diamond stars.
是国王在皇后上一年生日的时候送给她的那条
the king presented to the queen on her last birthday.
当白金汉带着它离开的时候 我还不知道呢
When the Buckingham went after the evidence, I do not notice.
把一切你掌握不到的情况给我列个单子
Bear me a resentation of everything you do not know.
否则在你采取行动时白金汉就到加莱了
or Buckingham will be in Calais before you have done.
不不不 求你了 救命啊
no, no, no, please, help.
哈哈 是个石头
Haha, it's a stone.
你欺骗我啊?
You have deceived me?
竟然骗我
Deceived me!
考虑到你是个卖国贼 起来吧 我的朋友
Thinking that you are a traitor, rise, my friend.
我还可以说些什么啊 伯纳修先生
Mr. Bonacieux, what can I say?
我发现我们对你的怀疑实在是太不公平了
I finded our suspicion about you was entirely unjust.
主教握着我的手叫我"朋友"
The Cardinal has taken my hand and called me "friend".
我们应该给你更好的待遇
Oh, we must make you better manage than that.
把这一百个金币拿去吧 原谅我
Take these hundred pistoles and forgive me.
我?原谅您吗?哦您千万别这么说
I? Forgive your Eminence? Oh you can not ring that.
我意思是…我是什么啊?我什么都不是
I mean... what am I? I'm nothing...better...
比无名小卒还低等
less than nothing.
朋友你太慷慨了…好吧
Friend you are generous... well then.
来这儿…我还是希望你能常来
Up here... that I still hope that you would come and.
看看我
visit me again.
那么我们就能一起聊聊天
so that we could talk together until our next meeting.
他说我们可以一起聊聊天
He said that we are going to talk together.
这样不好吗?
Isn't that lovely?
我想我下赌注挺大的 突然间从他老婆那儿得到灵感
I think I have done all the gamble, suddenly inspired by his wife.
他没觉得我胆怯吧?
He didn't think I'm frightened, did he?
这个英勇的白金汉公爵 肯定会戴上项链的
the gallant Buckingham will most certainly wear those diamond stars.
马上给在英国的文特尔夫人去个信儿
Send word immediately the Mrs. De Winter, in England.
她和白金汉走挺近的 让她拿俩个钻石来
She used to get close to him, and obtain 2 of the stones.
你去确定一下 让她一拿到就给我
You go there to make sure, see that she bring them to me immediately.
至于她怎么拿到那就是她的事儿了
How she gets them is her affair.
你喜欢这个地方吗?非常便宜
You like this place? It's very cheap.
等等 我可以赢点儿钱的
Wait a minute. I can win some money for us.
就是他 买他吧 他会赢的
Ha he's the one. He's the one. He will win.
哦 来吧  孩子 来吧
Oh, come on, dear boy, come on!
那都不够吃饭钱啊
But that's not even enough to pay for dinner.
我饿死了
I'm starving!
来点儿鸡肉吧 星期三鸡肉总是很好的传统
What about some chicken? That's alway popular on Wednesday.
今天是周二啊
It's Tuesday.
- 要切吗?先生 - 不不不 你有没有一些更好的东西啊
- Chop? sir? - Oh no no no no quite rocky what about hot for something really well?
让他做这个吧
Tell him to cook this will you?
你有毛有翼了吧?
You great over grown child.
我知道你们想干什么了 喂…
I know what you are doing. Oy...
这样好吗?
Alright?
我们应该为我们带来的不便负责任的
we should cover the inconvenience sir.
哦 看那羽毛
Oh, look at the feathers.
你听到叫声了吗?
Do you heard the cry?
您听到了吗夫人?阁下说想看您跳舞
You hear Madam? His Eminence wants to see you dance.
他建议以您的名义举办个舞会
He suggests invite you a ball in your honor.
这样能让你高兴吗?
Will that please you?
您高兴 我就高兴了
What pleases your majesty is delight to me.
那么就在维纳酒店吧 到时候我们好好享受
So at the hotel Ville, until it starts we should be regale.
舞会 芭蕾和戏服和…还有什么?
Ball and Ballett and costumes and ... What more?
哦 对了 你可以戴我送给您的那条钻石项链
Oh, yes. You will be able to wear the diamond stars I gave you.
那么皇后就会闪耀全场了
That will crown her majesty that evening.
- 钻石项链? - 对啊 那条项链 给你的生日礼物
- Diamond stars? - Yes the stars. My present to you.
为什么不呢?你觉得它们不合适吗?
Why not? Do you not think they're becoming?
不不不 很漂亮
Yes, yes, sir. They are beautiful.
那你为什么这个表情?我希望看到你戴上它们
Then why wish you them worn? I wish you to wear them.
我期待那个舞会 夫人
I depend the ball in, Madam.
这鸟可抓得我真紧啊 它都要把我眼泪逼出来了
This bird has got the grip on me, he's brought tears in my eyes.
脚都抓进我手腕里面了
They bite into my wrist.
你看到眼泪了吗?
See the tears?
在舞会的时候 戴着钻石
During the ball, wearing diamonds stars.
你想看到皇后跳舞吗?
You want to see the queen dance?
您真是越来越浪漫了 即使在神圣的主面前
You are becoming a romantic, under your sacred matresses.
即使是一个主教也是有弱点的陛下
Even a cardinal has weaknesses, your Majesty.
难道国王就没有吗?看到眼泪了吗?
Well as the king has not eh? See the tears?
一下的交谈发生在
The following conversation took place.
伯纳修夫人在宫殿的卧室里面
in the bedchamber of Madam. Bonacieux at the palace.
皇后说: "我不知道该如何是好 "
The queen said: "I am lost, I'm lost".
伯纳修夫人说: "殿下 ""康斯坦丝 我该怎么办"
Madam. Bonacieux said: "Majesty. " "Constance, I am lost. "
"殿下 ""我该怎么办啊康斯坦丝?"
"Majesty. " "What I can do, Constance? ".
"我们可以把项链从白金汉公爵那儿拿回来啊"
"We can get the stars back, Lord Buckinham. "
"在十四天之内吗?从伦敦?不可能的"
"In fourteen days, from London? I'm lost. "
"殿下 十四天内信使可以带着信
"Majesty, in fourteen days a messenger can reach
从伦敦回到巴黎"
London and return to Paris with the starts ".
"信使?谁啊?我一个人都信不过
"A messenger, who? I can trust no one.
那个恶魔哪儿都有眼线
That devil has inform everywhere.
那个邪恶猥琐讨厌卑鄙的小人!
That evil filthy revolting wretched man, evil filthy revolting evil man.
还称呼自己为代表教堂的人 "
calls himself a man of a church. "
不是我说的
According to this.
我会找到一个信使的殿下
I will find a messenger Majesty.
我相信一个人 我发誓
I trusted one. I swear it.
他可以把你的信交给白金汉公爵
He can carry a letter from you to Lord Buckingham.
对对 一封信 我应该写一封信
Yes, yes a letter. I shall write.
以我的名义 以我生命的名义
It's on my honor and from my life.
你有人可相信吗?
You have someone you can trust with that?
殿下 他不会失败的
Majesty, he will not fail.
- 噢 - 噢
- Oh. - Oh.
这是为了皇后 她处于可怕的危险当中
It is for the queen. She's in terrible danger.
除非这封信可以马上带到伦敦去
Unless this letter could be taken immediately to London.
如果你可以马上启程 她除了我没有别人可以相信了
If you could set out at once. She has no one to trust but me.
而我除了你 也信不过别人
And I could trust no one but you.
噢 这封信是那么危险 来睡觉吧 我美丽的康斯坦丝
Oh letter's dangerous. Come to bed, Constance my small chicken.
我会对你好好的…
And I will...
如果你答应我送这封信 我就什么都答应你
Oh I will do anything you ask if you promise you'll take the letter.
这封信我什么都不知道啊 我美丽的康斯坦丝
Oh what do I know about the letters oh my beautiful Constance.
我只知道我好多天晚上没睡好了
I have been sweep days and so many nights.
- 不 我认真的 - 你觉得我不认真吗?
- No, I'm serious. - You think I'm not?
但是你现在必须去伦敦了
Oh you must go to London now.
必须 那是你说的 我倒不见得
Oh it must because you say so.
我不想帮你带这封信
What I don't wish to be trusted at me.
我告诉你为什么吧
and I'll tell you why.
因为这封可疑的信充满了阴谋
because that so very suspicious letter smacks up intrigue.
噢 康斯坦丝 康斯塔斯…
Oh, Constance, Constance ...
是的 阴谋 我非常好奇皇后给你灌什么迷汤了
Yes, intrigue. I'm very much intrigue of your queen has done for you!
我又被侮辱又害怕还被困在巴士底狱里面
Insulted terrified and me tracked to the Bastille.
那可是巴士底狱啊亲 我困哪儿都不想被困在那儿啊
The Bastille I tell you I don't wish to be sent to the Bastille.
因为那里有很多地牢还有很多恐怖的用刑的工具
because it's got many deep dungeon and terrible instruments of torture.
都是一些毫无同情心的人来行刑的
operated by unsympathetic men.
他们会把人的重要部位切下来
and they slip very important parts off people.
如果不是大主教
If it hadn't been for the Cardinal...
- 大主教? - 是的 大主教
- The Cardinal? - Yes, the Cardinal.
你以为就只有你上头有人吗
You think you alone have friends in high places.
我告诉你吧
Well let me tell you then.
大主教握着我的手还和我称兄道弟呢
The Cardinal took my hand and he called me "friend".
还给我这包钱
And he gave me this purse.
- 你见过大主教了? - 对啊 他还想再和我聊天呢
- You have seen the Cardinal? - Yes, he wishes to talk to me again.
我再告诉你多些内幕吧我的夫人
And allow me tell you something else my lady.
他可不太喜欢这些阴谋
He doesn't much go on this type of intrigue.
告诉我 这封信是给谁送去的?
Tell me, to whom with that letter go?
如果你不想带那就不关你的事儿
It's nothing to you if you do not wish to carry it.
很好夫人
Very well Madam.
如果你不想和我一起睡觉
If you don't wish to go to bed with me.
那我就要走了
I shall have to leave you.
我要赴一个很重要的约会
For an very important appointment.
一个很重要的约会
A very important appointment.
- 噢 是你 - 就是我
- Oh, you! - me.
- 你听见了? - 每个词都听见了 - 你都知道了
- And you heard? - Every word. - All that you know.
除了你和皇后需要一个侍者
Only that you and the queen need the services of the gentleman.
这个人要英勇 谨慎 积极 杰出的 忠诚的
who is gallant, gerageous discrete, active, brilliant, loyal.
我就可以了 我也知道去伦敦的路啊
And I am one, and I also know the way to London.
而你的好丈夫现在估计在去找大主教的路上
And your good husband who's probably on his way to cardinal.
现在还可以给我提供路费
this moment is thoughtfully provided my expenses.
但是我可以相信你吗?
But can I trust you?
相信我?相信我?噢这个问题
Trust me? Trust me? Oh the question.
你可以相信我 因为我爱你
You can trust me, because I love you.
你也爱我
And you love me.
如果你不爱我 那你就是有点问题
or if you do not, there is something wrong with you.
你必须要发誓你绝不透露出
You must swear never to reveal the name of the.
这封信的接受者的名字
person to whom may goes.
哦 以我的名义
On, my honor.
他是白金汉公爵
His name is the duke of Buckingham.
- 这边请 先生 - 你的丈夫行动真快啊
- This way, sir. - He moves quickly the husband of yours.
噢 快点儿
Oh, hurry!
哈哈 这些事情老发生
Ha ha, it happened all the time.
康斯坦丝!康斯坦丝!
Constance! Constance!
她走了
She's gone!
因为你不接受那封信
Because you are not the way you accept the letter.
哦 那封信
Oh, letter!
她肯定逃去皇宫避难了
She's out of flip to the palace.
这里没有人了 蜡烛还是温的
There's no one here. The candle still warm.
那去大路往小路的方向搜 快点
Then take the street to the path, quickly.
她肯定走不远
She can't be gone far.
这封信 你老婆提到白金汉公爵没有?
This letter, your wife mentioned, the duke of Buckingham?
没有 先生 没有名字
No, monsieur, no name.
这个叫达特尼昂的家伙在你这儿住 是吧?
This fellow D'Artagnan, lodges with you, does he not?
嗯 我们要给这个先生找个冷点的地方安置
Hmm, we should find a cold lodging for monsieur D'Artagnan.
达特尼昂和他的朋友们要警醒
and his friends as a precaution.
- 安置在巴士底狱里面 - 然后呢?
- In the Bastille. - And afterwards?
然后就没有然后了
In the Bastille there is no "afterwards".
什么?
What?
这个男人又侮辱我
That man in his time has insulted me, broke my.
把我爹给我的剑弄断 还让我翻在地上
father's sword had me clapped at the ground.
还这样对我爱的女人
and has abused the woman I love.
他真是很麻烦
He's inconveniet.
让我告诉你一些关于你提到
Let me tell you something about this.
的这个"麻烦人"的事情
"inconvenient" the gentleman of yours.
他教罗什福尔
He's name is Rochefort.
他是大主教的活武器而且非常致命啊
He's the cardinal's living blade and he's deadly.
你俩能不能跑快点啊? 散步了吧啊?
Will you rambling move your way you ballocks.
十五比零
Fifteen none.
再买十五个
Fifteen more.
十五比四
Fifteen four.
三十比十五
Thirty fifteen.
关于罗什福尔就是这些了
And that's for Rochefort.
如果有一天你在街上看到他迎面走来
If you see him walking at the other side of the road.
就让他经过吧
one day then well let him cross over that's all.
阿拉米斯!扫过那边去
Aramis!Scout over the gate.
- 这是唯一的机会了 - 你去吧
- Your only chance. - You for the galement.
有没有罗什福尔
With Rochefort or no Rochefort.
我都要带着信去伦敦
I have to get to London with this letter.
这是皇后的任务
It's on the queen's business.
14天之后我要带着回复回来巴黎
and I have to return back with an answer within 14 days.
你可能走不出5公里
The cuttings friends hunting you and get 5 miles.
游戏结束了 决赛
Game over and final set.
好样的
Good looking.
- 那就是说你决定要做邮差了 - 嗯
- Say you want to set the deliver. - hmm.
如果我们四个都去的话就有可能成事
What if the four of us go, it should get there.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
给你这是明天晚饭
There you go tomorrow's dinner sir.
我兄弟的工资都押你俩身上了
My brother's wage on the hugo for the paper see that gambling on you two.
收拾收拾东西吧 我们去伦敦
now get your things we're arriving to London.
伦敦?
London?
我有没钱了吗?亲爱的
Well did I being poor again dear?
灵魂已经腐烂了 你们不该继承上帝的国土
Souls has been corrupted. You shall not inherite the kingdom of god.
- 我们什么时候走? - 马上
- When do we leave? - at once.
去哪儿找马?
where should I get our horses?
我们把仆人都辞了
We take out the servants.
一个男人可能不经意泄露自己的秘密
the gentlemen may reveal the secrets by accident.
但是一个仆人会故意把你卖了
The servants invariably sells them.
还有一但我们遇上这样的事
On another thing once we meet.
在路上如果我们有一个倒下了
On this road one of us go down.
其他的三个要拿着信继续走
The other three gone with the letter.
其他的人就要抓紧机会逃命 同意吗?
the one to four take his chance, agree?
没有人会问自己的命运吗
No one ask delicate fate.
没有人想知道自己什么时候归天吗?
the calls in which may being expected to die?
当我们打仗的时候 国王给我们原因了吗
When we go on a campaign, does the king give us a reason?
- 他说杀我们就冲 - 好的 好的
- He says fight and you fight. - I do I do.
那么当我们该死的时候我们就接受命运吧
Well let's going to be killed where we told to.
一个人的生活总是要不停解决问题的
His life worth so many questions.
小心那个拿着包的小子
Careful with that bagged boy.
荷兰人肯定会给他超过一年的钱
The dutches will surely pay you more than a year...
我去找她
I'll go for her.
- 愿上帝与你同在 - 哦你也是 在这个阳光普照的早上
- God be with you sir. - Oh and you too, sir on this fine morning.
- 你想喝一杯吗? - 很荣幸 - 你会为大主教干杯吗?
- Will you toast sir? - With pleasure. - will you drink to hell for the cardinal?
呃 非常高兴先生 如果你也可以为国王而干杯
Glad to sir, if you then join me for the to toast of king.
我不认得什么国王 只认得大主教
I recognize no king but the cardinal.
哦你醉了先生
Oh you're drunk sir.
对此只有一个答案
There's only one answer for that.
你要为此付出代价的
You will pay for it now sir if you please.
这些破事儿!干掉这个人然后尽快跟上我们
This is shit folly!Kill the fellow and follow us as soon as you can, will you?
来吧
Come on!
他能行吗?
Would already done, three!
可能安全的很 那个人是醉猫啊
Probably safe enough. The fellow is drunk.
去做祷告足够清醒了
He get sober enough for him to came on god.
该死的!看!毁了我的衣服
Damn you! Look! ruined!
走开!小心!
Go away! Mind out!
来吧
Come on!
来吧来吧
Come on! Come on!
放下
Drop it!
同样的命运可能在前面十公里的地方等着我们
The same fate awaits us perhaps ten miles aheads.
但是至少现在我们还是安全的
But at least we should be safe enough till then.
前进
Forward!
你告诉我
You do tell me.
叛国罪…虽然是叛国罪
Treason...treason it may be.
但是我还是对法国女人的魅力感到折服
But I will maintain the beauty.
法国女人是最迷人的
of French women about of all others.
的确不能听信英国人的花言巧语
We really believe in Englishmen can anyone?
去睡觉吧 菲尔顿
Go to bed, Felton!
漫漫长夜独自斟酌啊
Long period and faces mumping at bed time.
我什么想法都没有
Nothing's given in my mind.
一个都不允许上船
As I can't carry a anyone's hand.
除非你有大主教的通行证
unless you have a pass from the cardinal.
我有啊
I have a pass.
这个早上我能做的只有保证没有人可以离开
All I can do this morning is that no one was leave.
如果没有白金汉公爵的签名的话
without the signiture of the Buckingham.
很好 我一个小时之后回来
Very well I'll be back in one hour.
但是请您多注意一点
But the Register sailed and keep a close watch sir.
不要出现任何错误也不要让任何人离开
any kind of mistakes who are trying to escape.
你可以帮我一个忙 先生
You are on a position to do me a favour, sir.
你口袋里面的那个通行证
That pass you have in your pocket.
如果你把它给我
if you handed over to me now.
那么会给我们双方带来不少方便
it will save us all a great deal of inconvenience.
你就是那个骑黄马那个二货
You are the gascon rascal with the yellow horse.
和那几个剑客在街角上吹牛
so bazoo on the street corners with the musketeers.
街角…你措辞不错啊
Street cornors...you have carefully avoid them monsieur.
独眼龙
Cyclops.
你那其他三个同伙呢?
Where are your three accomplices?
他们会做得好得多的
It would have done better ...
我啊 是我
Me, it's me!
别担心 先生 我来了
Don't worry, sir, I'm coming.
来啦
Coming!
我说吧
I told you.
先生 你要死了吗?
Monsieur, are you killed?
还没
Not quite.
就是刺伤了一点点
Just a scratch longer rip.
哦 上天 你对你的子民做了什么?
Oh, father, what you almost did to your son?
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
失去知觉了 先生 我要干掉他吗?
A lost monsieur. No it's only stoned. Should I kill him?
当然不要了 把他手腕绑起来塞住他嘴巴
Certaily not. Just tie his wrist and gag him.
我们给他机会让他血流致死
We give him the chance to bleeding to dead.
但是我们并没有杀了他
But we are not murder him.
但是这个通行证只给一个人过的
But the pass is for only one person.
是一个人啊 这个是仆人
I'm only one person. That is a servant.
我明白了 好吧
I see, alright.
你还好吧
Are you alright?
看!多佛港!
Look! Dover!
好了 这是我的
Alright it's mine.
陛下
My Lord!
哦 是那个善妒的情人啊
So, it's the jealous lover.
你不是准备来英国
I trust you haven't come to England to.
和我再干一架的吧
fast another quarrel on me?
我不认识字
I'm afraid I can not read.
你在路上多久了
How long have you been on the road?
六天了 陛下
Six days, my lord.
那么我们要快
Then so we must buzzle.
快点 我们要快啊
Come on Plachet, we must buzzle.
哦 天啊 我已经很快了
Oh, god, I'm buzzling.
快点 先生 让马儿跑起来
Come, sir! At the gallop!
一 二…
One, two ...
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
她是我的女神
She is my dearty.
给你项链
Here they are.
我还想永远留下它
I hope to keep them always.
天啊 两颗钻不见了!
God, in heaven! There are two of them missing.
- 不见了?为什么? - 别激动 让我想想
- Missing? Why? - Right away, let me think.
两周以前的舞会上 12颗还完好无损
I hold 12 of them in the ball two weeks ago.
文特尔伯爵夫人
The Countess de Winter.
我的天
My God!
无神论者美丽的代价
It's a pretty price to pay for infidelity.
她现在肯定已经在法国了
She would be in France by now.
菲尔顿
Felton!
- 被偷了? - 被大主教的间谍偷了
- They have been stolen? - By cardinal spy!
法式麻烦
French trouble!
菲尔顿 我的秘书 我要起一份命令
Felton, my secretary. I want an ordering.
- 有人还有钢笔吗? - 有支铅笔
- Someone got a pen? - Got a pencil.
写个命令给海峡港口
Write an ordering saying to the channel ports.
没我同意任何船只不得离开港口
No vessels is to sail without my agree.
如果国王问起
If the king ask any questions.
就说我正在筹备对法开战
tell him I'm thinking a war with France.
然后清开这里到多佛的路段
And keep the road to Dover clear.
六天了 对吧?
6 days here eh?
你要尽你所能把项链还回去
You should kill youself return these stars.
而且要准时及时
to the queen in time soon.
但是…那两颗不见了的呢?
But ...the missing ones?
欧赖利 给这些估估价
O'Reilly, put a price on these.
一个值多少钱
Each one they worth.
不是英国货
Not English, not English.
我认为…500镑吧
I'd say er...500 pounds.
做两个这样的要多久
How long to make 2 of them?
一个星期?
A week?
我给你5000镑一个
I'll pay you 5, 000 pounds each.
如果你能在后天完成的话
if they are finished the day after tomorrow.
成交!你可以去给我妻子传达一声我不回家睡觉了吗
Done! Could I invite to my wife that I won't be coming home?
我会办的更妥的 杰克逊
I'll do better than that, Jackson.
派一辆马车去欧赖利夫人那儿
A carriage in that score to carvery.
把她接过来 给她准备一间房间
from Ms. O'Reilly, prepare rooms for her.
哦 这么好啊
Oh, that's nice.
- 你受伤了吗? - 没什么
- Have you hurt yourself? - It's nothing.
漂亮啊 漂亮啊
Beautiful, beautiful.
如果我说他们和你的眼睛非常般配 是不是恭维呢?
Will you be a compliment to say if they match your eyes?
这么恭维真是太阳从西边出来了
Unusual gallantry.
你一般的幽默感和我的真心能相提并论啊
Your normal humor will be compared them to my heart.
真够犀利的讽刺
a delicate mean.
上面是大主教 下面是皇后
up cardinal, down queen.
我们快点
We move fast.
试一下 把欧赖利做的两个新的找出来
There sir, the cast O'Reilly's 2 new ones if you can.
现在 以我们都在为之服务的伟大的女士的名义
Now, for the honor of the great lady who we both serve.
以下把这项链及时归还的任务就交给你了
It's for you to see that you receive them in time.
- 以我们赖以为生的后土之名 - 那你呢先生
- Where all we just stand on living. - And you, sir ...
我该怎么报答你?
How can I ever repay you?
陛下 让我们彼此都搞清楚
My lord, let us understand one and other.
你是英国人 而且你是法国的敌人
You are an English man, and an enemy of France.
你不欠我什么
You owe me nothing.
但是我所做的一切都是为了皇后
but what I've done I've done for the queen.
和那个对我来说和皇后对于你一样重要的女人
and for another who is as dear to me as the queen to you.
我自愿付出的
I'll take my lieber.
请您原谅 我刚忘记英国是个岛
Your raises pardon, I had forgotten England is an island.
我怎么过岸?
How do I get off?
你会在看到马 在旧丹佛港有船在那里等着
You will find ride horses at the clear old Dover where there is a ship waiting.
先生 就算是朋友的回报你也不愿意接受吗?
Monsieur, you will take no reward from a friend?
你起码收下这个…和敌人给的这个
Will you at least accept this...and this from an enemy?
那就不同了
That is different.
- 我很累啊 - 我也是!我们快到了
- I'm tired. - So am I. We're almost there.
- 但是我很浑身酸痛 - 哦 拜托 练练你的腰吧
- But I am sore. - Oh, come on, put your back in drill.
要起火了
I got fire.
- 我们要换马了 - 认得这个地方吗?
- We need to change horses. - Recognize this place?
这是最后一个我们都活着的地方
The last place on earth when we all alive together.
到我们相聚的日子
Till we meet again my friends.
离那儿已经不远了
Will not be long.
绳子啊 快点
The rope, quickly.
马啊
The horse.
你握住啊老天啊 你在哪儿
Hold on for god's sake. Where are you?
- 拉啊看门的 拉啊!- 快点儿啊
- Pull it gate man pull it!- Quickly!
他们估计要累趴下了
They probably sit down!
啊哈!
Ah ha!
是时候了
It's about time.
啊
Ah.
- 快点 快点! - 得瑟吧! - 为什么你总是在后面?
- Come on, come on! - Show off! - Why are you alway lefting behind?
- 你听到那个声音了吗? - 那坑爹的口音
- Did you hear that voice? - That unfortunate accent!
兄弟同心 其利断金!
All for one and one for all!
我妻子就在里面
My wife is in there then.
他和所有重要的人跳舞
She dance with all the best people.
有时候向我招招手
And sometimes she waves at me.
有时候也和我跳舞
sometimes she dance with me.
夫人 为什么你不戴钻石项链呢?
Madam, why you are not wearing the diamond stars?
你知道我特别想看看这条项链
You knew I particularly wants to see them.
陛下 这么多人我怕会不见了
Majesty, in this big crowd I fear that I might lose them.
你错了 我就是给你这个礼物让你…让你…
You are wrong. I made you this present to...to...
供自己瞻仰
to adore youself.
我真是非常不满意
I'm highly displeased.
如果陛下你喜欢的 我可以让人马上送到宫殿来
If your Majesty pleases, I can send to the palace for them.
好吧…马上送来
Do so...and immediately.
继续吧 雷吉 满上
Go ahead, Reggie, filling up.
我正尽力 我正给你满上
I'm doing my best, and I'm filling up.
他正走向我呢
He's coming over to me now.
- 他不喜欢吃那个 他吃了吗? - 是的
- Not his have for one a mind! Did he take...? - Yes.
皇后看上去很苍白
Her Majesty is really pale, I thought, sire?
我可以稍微把您的注意力吸引过来
May I respectly direct your Majesty's attention to.
到盒子里的甜点上吗
to this sweets in this box.
我肯定你会非常感兴趣
I feel sure you will agree there are a royal confession.
什么意思?
What does this mean?
没什么 如果皇后有项链
Nothing. Only if the queen has the stars.
我就非常疑惑了
which I have very much doubt.
数数项链里的钻石数 你应该只能数到10个
Count them sire, if you should find only 10.
问问她剩下的两个怎么回事吧
ask her Majesty what could possibly happen to the other 2.
我告诉你…如果没有正式邀请函没有人可以进去
I told you... No one, no one may enter without a proper invitation.
这是主教的命令
It's the cardinal's order.
- 您在说一遍 - 我说… - 不用说了
- I beg your pardon, sir? - I said... - It doesn't matter.
加油 就是这样 加油 再来一次
Come on, that's it!Come on!Again!
就是这样!再来一次
That's it! Again.
哦夫人 他还是可能会来的
Oh madam, he may still come!
我确定他会来
I feel sure he will.
怎么会呢 康斯坦丝
How can he, Constance?
没用的 结束了
It's no use. It's over.
我会吐的 慢点
I'm gonna be sick, slow down!
那肯定是康斯坦丝
It has to be Constance.
听到小号声就放烟花
Remember light the firework when you hear the trump.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
快点
Quickly!
- 达特尼昂! - 什么?
- D'Artagnan! - What?
哦!
Oh!
别担心康斯坦丝我快到了
Don't worry Constance I'm almost there.
下来
come down!
对不起
Sorry!
你们怎么停下来了
Oh why are you stopping gentlemen?
请让一让?
please?
守卫!拦住他!跟着熊
Guards! Stop him! Follow that bear!
我们是老朋友了
We are old friends!
你们都来拯救我了
You all come to rescue me.
谢谢老天你们都还活着
Thank God you are alive!
做的真好
Well done!
你们能帮我上去吗
Can you get me up there?
现在
Now.
你好
Hello!
等等 等等
Wait a minute!Wait a minute!
他扯烂了我们的地毯
He's torn our carpet.
快点兄弟们
Quickly gentleman.
三 四 五…
Three, four, five ...
一 二 三 四…
One, two, three, four ...
一 二 三 四…站住
One, two, three, four ... stand still.
过来 来来来...
Get on, come, come come come...
请借过一下
Excuse me, please.
谢谢你 夫人 你满足了我的心愿
I'll thank you madam for accomplish my wishes.
但是你是不是丢了两颗钻石呢
but I believe you have lost 2 stars.
我把它们带给你了
and I bring them to you.
陛下 你多给了我两个
Sire, you bring me 2 more!
你太慷慨了!现在我有十四个了
How kind of you!Now I should have 14.
14个?13 14…
14? 13...14...
大主教 这是怎么回事儿
What does it mean cardinal?
事实是…陛下
It means...sire.
我想把这两颗钻石送给皇后殿下
that I wished to present those stars to her Majesty.
但是又不敢自己送
and not daring myself to walk with them.
我把它们通过您来给皇后
I gave them to her through you.
哦 我真是太受宠若惊了主教
I'm terribly grateful, your Eminence.
我肯定这两颗钻石比其他的十二个
I'm certain these 2 stars cost you.
都贵得多啊
much more than the other 12 of course.
你说是不是?陛下
isn't that, majesty?
阁下 达特尼昂设法进来舞会了
Eminence, D'Artagnan gained entry to the halltail.
的确是 我看出来了
Quite so.
你失败了 我也输了
You fail, and I lost.
在这个游戏中输了分数 您继续吧
I lost the point to the game, continue.
我们不把这个有勇无谋的小子找出来吗
we are not seeking him out, this boy, who is out of wititute.
找出来干什么?报仇吗?真是太奢侈的事
To what end? Revenge? That is an expensive luxury.
政治家也支付不起这样的损失啊
Statesmen can not afford it.
不用 我可以利用这个人
No, I could use such a man.
也许我还是得把他找出来
perhaps I shall seek him out afterall.
阁下您是一个玩游戏的行家 输得起
Your Eminence is a great player, great enough to lose.
但是我不喜欢输
I do not like to lose.
那您就做自己想做的事情吧夫人
You must suit yourself, my lady.
即使最后还是输了
For even in the end you should.
也要输得漂亮
do it and becoming grace.
我的心肝宝贝啊
Oh my darling darling darling.
我再也不会让你在外面这么危险的地方闯荡了
Never again will I let you go in such terrible danger.
哦 奔驰 挣扎 打架 战斗 那都是什么?
Oh, gallops, struggles, stemmish, frustos, too. What is that?
那都是一天的生活啊
It's a day's work.
但是最终能找到我心爱的美丽的康斯坦丝
but to find my beautiful Constance till the end.
你想我吗?
Did you miss me?
这真是一个蠢问题
A foolish question.
我帮他干活
I work for him!
年轻人 你现在是个火枪手了
Well young Gascon, now you are a musketeer.
都拿着国王的步枪
Carrying the king's muskets with honor.
现在你们是四个火枪手
Now you are the four musketeers.
现在我们是四个了
Now we are four.
我的老板!他正向你招手呢
My boss! He's waving to you!
现在我们整整齐齐的 别弄丢了
And there we are all. Don't drop it!
向国王致意
Oh, the king!